Venkitesh B S

E-mail: coolvenki1994@gmail.com

Contact: +91-8610245625

To work as a web developer for a company where I can apply my knowledge and abilities while learning new ones to help achieve the objectives of the company.

Summary

Graduated with a degree in information technology and have worked on end-to-end Web development projects, including requirement analysis, system analysis, design, coding, testing, documentation, and implementation utilizing a variety of technologies.

Career Summary

Total Experience: 9-years

Organization	Designation	Period
Box Of Tech	Software Engineer	Jan 2022- Till date
Kambaa incorporation	Web Developer	Oct 2020 to Jan 2022
Rasi Infotech Pvt Ltd	Software Developer	Feb 2018 to Sep 2020
P.S.G College of Technology	Programmer Analyst	Jan 2017 To Jan 2018
Tecnova Solutions	Junior Tester	Feb 2016 To Sep 2016.

Technical Skills

 $Core\ Php\ |\ CSS\ |Html\ |\ JavaScript|\ jQuery\ |Json|\ Laravel\ |MySQL|\ Reactjs|\ SQL|\ RestAPIs\ |Bootstrap\ |Team\ management|\ Angular$

Work Details

PROJECT - 1

- Project: D- Store (Ecommerce Product)
- Duration: 3 month
- Language: Html, CSS, Bootstrap, ¡Query, JavaScript
- Technology: Laravel Framework and MySQL.
- Team Size: 2 Member

PROJECT - 2

- Project: Garudaa Gold Chit and digi Gold Scheme (Product)
- Duration: 4 month

- Language: Html, CSS, BootStrap, JQuery, JavaScript
- Technology: Laravel Framework and Mysql.
- Team Size: 2 Member.

PROJECT - 3

- Project: Madurai Biriyani (Ecommerce web application and mobile app) -Link-
- Duration: 4 month
- Language: Html, CSS, BootStrap, JQuery, JavaScript
- Technology: Laravel Framework and Mysql.
- Team Size: 2 Member

PROJECT - 4

- Project: Interkart (Ecommerce web application and mobile app)
- Duration: 4 month
- Language: Html, CSS, BootStrap, JQuery, JavaScript
- Technology: Laravel Framework and Mysql.
- Team Size: 2 Member

ADDITIONAL PROJECTWORKS

- "Canadian Bilingual School" Website Developing using Laravel and MySQL. Languageused:Html, CSS, bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript.
- "Aspire Indian International School" Website Developingusing PHP. Language used: Html, CSS, Boot Strap, JQuery, JavaScript.
- "Eswar jewellers" Web Application using React. Languageused:React JS,BootStrap.
- "Zinger Pos" App Developing using React. Languageused:React JS,BootStrap.
- "Amr Sumangalee Jewellers" App Developing using React. Languageused:React JS,BootStrap.
- "Pakistan English School" Website Developing using Laravel and MySQL. Language: Html, CSS, Boot Strap, jQuery, JavaScript.

CERTIFICATION

- Completed HtmlEssential Training in linked in learning platform.
- Completed BootstrapEssential Training in linked in learning platform.
- Participated in two-dayworkshop titled Enterprise private Network and Network Security organize by computer society of India, Chennai.
- Undergone a Training in .Net at United Info Solution, Salem.
- Participated in two-dayworkshop titled Ethical Hacking organized by Mahendra Engineering College, Salem.
- Participated in one day national seminar on Html 5, Villupuram.
- Participated in one day national seminar on Emerging trends in computer vision and graphics.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

- Under Graduation (2012-2015) B. Tech(Information Technology) with 63% in Mahendra Engineering College (Under Anna University), Salem.
- **DIT**(2009-2012) with 90% in Salem Polytechnic College, Salem.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's name : Suresh B

Gender : Male

DateofBirth : 10/06/1994

Languages known: English (RWS), Tamil(RWS), Telugu(S)

DATE: Authentically

PLACE: Salem (B.S. VENKITESH)